Youth Paste is making you dumber. Let me explain.
The majority of all toothpaste have a toxic chemical in them that destroys an important
gland in your brain. This substance is known as fluoride. The government wants you to
think that fluoride is good for you and that it's safe, but that's just a lie. Fluoride
calcifies an important gland in your brain, known as the pineal gland. This gland is responsible
for many things like your circadian cycle and hormone secretion. Many also believe that
the pineal gland is the seed of the soul and is where you unlock higher consciousness.
Side effects of having a calcified pineal gland include a wide range of neuronal diseases
like Alzheimer's and also disruption of melatonin and serotonin levels. To combat this, you
have two options. Find a trusted brand of fluoride-free toothpaste or make your own toothpaste
by mixing coconut oil, baking soda, sea salt, and essential oils like mint. If they can't
get you with toothpaste, they'll try and get you with the tap water. There's a reason
fluoride is banned in many European countries. The United States has one of the most corrupt
systems in the world, all to keep you sick and dumb. Luckily, there are people trying
to expose this corruption like me. It's up to you to decide what you want to believe,
the lies or the real truth. Follow Divine Herbal Roots for more daily