okay I'll have it bring it to a report
in Sunday's Axios Jonathan Swan who I
think is extremely fair says this
president Trump as defending Rob Porter
and him publicly but privately he says
he's guilty
says the president told multiple people
that he believes the accusations against
Porter are true and finds him six four
sources have spoken directly with
President Trump and tell him his private
comments about the ex aide whose two
ex-wives accuse me of violent acts have
been brutal so the president is just as
outraged as many Americans about the
alleged domestic abuse which looks
pretty strong the evidence strong
against Porter why wouldn't he say that
publicly or do you think Jonathan Swan
is wrong well I don't know if he's gonna
say that publicly or not and I've not
spoken with the president about this but
I can say you know we leaned on a
process here at the White House and
quite frankly as soon as we found out
about this on Tuesday by Wednesday Rob
Porter was gone the president has been
very clear that all forms of abuse all
forms of a battery against women he
hasn't said and disgusting right but he
hasn't you haven't talked to him today I
mean obviously he said that multiple
times in the past but in this particular
instance you're talking about sources
that I can't verify because I'm not had
that conversation with him but I know
for a fact I've talked to the president
about issues surrounding this type of
behavior and he finds a disgusting sure
well the abuse allegations that you know
these stories are horrific they're
they're bad stories but something else
that is just as troubling is apparently
mr. Porter did not ultimately have his
security clearance because of the
problems in his past is the White House
going through everybody at the White
House so close to the president making
sure okay this guy's got it this guy's
got it wait a minute this person doesn't
maybe that that person should not be so
close to the president look that's a
process as I mentioned before but it's a
process done by career officials in the
federal government at the FBI and other
agencies so on purpose for
administration after administration
whether it was Bill Clinton whether it
was a George W Bush whether it's Barack
Obama the White House doesn't interfere
in those in those processes and they
keep going forward because we can't have
a handle on that that's something for
outside entities to look at okay you
can't stop the problem you and
Huckabee Sanders well y'all get together
and maybe advise him and talk to him
about this is an opportunity when he can
come out against domestic violence when
those pictures are horrific they were
absolutely but the president has been
out against domestic violence for a long
time he didn't in the Oval Office the
thing you're probably been talking about
he was asked specifically about Rob
Porter the president deplore it thinks
that domestic violence is grotesque he
said that on multiple occasions and
there's no place for it in this country
there's no place for it in this White
House and the president won't stand for
it all right
Hogan did Lee join it